[{"question": "  oh, and then monica joked that she wouldn\u0092t go out with a guy like chandler...", "answer": "   hi there.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": "  hi! rachel and bonnie: hi!", "answer": " rachel was just helping me out. my head got all sunburned.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " awww.", "answer": "  thanks a million.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " oh, you\u0092re welcome a million.", "answer": "   okay, i\u0092ll see you in our room.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": "  oh my god.", "answer": " i know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": "  okay, i gotta go.", "answer": " whoa! what?! why?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " well, i-i gotta go break up with bonnie.", "answer": " here?! now?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " well, yeah. i can\u0092t-i can\u0092t stay here all night, and if i go in there she\u0092s-she\u0092s gonna wanna... do stuff.", "answer": " well, can\u0092t you tell her that you are not in the mood?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " no, she likes that. yeah. faking sleep doesn\u0092t work either, i can\u0092t tell you how many mornings i woke up with her...", "answer": "  whoa-ho.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " whoa-oh, okay! yeah, why am i telling you that?", "answer": " i don\u0092t know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " yeah, yeah.  it wasn\u0092t every morning.", "answer": " oh, making it worse!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " so i guess you\u0092d like to know how it all happened.", "answer": " i-i mean i, well i think i can figure it out. i guess y'know i was born, and everyone started lying their asses off!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " noo! no! it wasn\u0092t like that i... remember how i told you how lily, frank, and i we were, we were close. well, we were, we were very close.", "answer": " how close?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " well, the-the three of us we were, kind of umm, a couple.", "answer": " i don\u0092t even know how that would work!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " well, we were...", "answer": "  i\u0092m not asking!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " well, any how, some how i got pregnant, and, and i was scared. i was stupid and sellfish, and i was 18 years old. i mean, you remember what it\u0092s like to be eighteen years old?", "answer": " yeah. let\u0092s see, my had mom killed herself, and my dad had run off, and i was living in a gremlin with a guy named cindy who talked to his hand.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " well, i\u0092m so sorry. i thought i was leaving you with the best parents in the world, i didn\u0092t even hear about your mom and dad til a couple of years ago, and by then you were already grown up. i don\u0092t know, you\u0092re here, and i would, i would really, i would like to get to know you.", "answer": " yeah, well, everybody does! i\u0092m a really cool person. and y'know you had 29 years to find that out, but you didn\u0092t even try! y'know what, you walked out on me, and i\u0092m just, i\u0092m gonna do the same thing to you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " wait!", "answer": " i don\u0092t ever want to see you again!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": "  shoot! we\u0092re out of soda.", "answer": "  oh, i\u0092ll go out and get you some.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " really?!", "answer": " nope! because i\u0092m not your boyfriend.  hey pheebs, how did it go?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " i found a dried up seashores.", "answer": " sweety, what are you talking about?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " whoa, wait, pheebs, wait a second! don\u0092t you wanna stay here and talk about it?", "answer": " no. i\u0092m just, i wanna, i need to be alone.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": "  monica!", "answer": " oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " it\u0092s over.", "answer": " oh, was it awful?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " i wrote you a letter.", "answer": " ohh! thank you! i like mail.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": "  it\u0092s just some things i\u0092ve been thinking about. some things about us, and before we can even think about the two of us getting back together, i just need to know how you feel about this stuff.", "answer": " okay.  wow, it\u0092s-it\u0092s 5:30 in the morning.  so, i\u0092d better get cracking on this baby.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " well, i\u0092ll be waiting for you, just come up when you\u0092re done.", "answer": " okay, i\u0092ll be up in,  18 pages. front and back. very exciting.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": "  hey!  what happened to you? why didn\u0092t you come up?", "answer": " done!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " you just finished?", "answer": " well, i wanted to be thorough. i mean this-this is clearly very, very important to you, to us! and so i wanted to read every word carefully, twice!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " so umm, does it?", "answer": " i\u0092m sorry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " does it?", "answer": " does it? does it? yeah, i wanted to give that whole \u0091does it?\u0092 part just another glance.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " what are you talking about, ross, you just said that you read it twice! look, y'know what, either it does or it doesn\u0092t, and if you have to even think about it...", "answer": "  no, rach, no. i don\u0092t, i don\u0092t, i don\u0092t have to think about it, in fact, i\u0092ve decided, i\u0092ve decided that, that it.......does.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " are you sure?", "answer": " oh, sure! i\u0092m sure.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " all right, there\u0092s a nuclear holocaust, i\u0092m the last man on earth. would you go out with me?", "answer": " ennnh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " i\u0092ve got canned goods.", "answer": "  hey, you guys! take a look at this!  check this baby out, dug me a hole!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " oh no! no!! my hole!!", "answer": "  ow!! ow!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": "  what?! what?!! what is it?!", "answer": " jellyfish sting! oh, it hurts! it hurts!! it hurts!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " well, can we help?! you want us to take you back to the house?!", "answer": " it\u0092s like two miles!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " yeah, and i\u0092m a little tired from digging the hole.", "answer": " oh damn the jellyfish. damn all the jellyfish!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " we\u0092ve got to do something!", "answer": " well, there\u0092s really only one thing you can do.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " what?! what is it?!", "answer": " you\u0092re gonna have to pee on it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " what?!! gross!!", "answer": " don\u0092t blame me, i saw it on the discovery channel.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " y'know what, he\u0092s right. there\u0092s something like uh, ammonia in that, that like kills the pain.", "answer": " well forget it! it doesn\u0092t hurt that  baaad!!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " how was the beach?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " nothing, i don\u0092t know.", "answer": " what happened?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " nothing. i\u0092m gonna take a shower.", "answer": " me too!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " me too.", "answer": " okay, i\u0092m gonna put this  in the car.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " ooh, i have to go pack.  it really does?", "answer": " it does. it really and truly does.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " she wants me to take responsibility for everything that went wrong in our relationship. i mean she goes on for five pages about, about how i was unfaithful to her!   we were on a break!!!!!", "answer": " oh my god! if you say that one more time, i\u0092m gonna break up with you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " fine! fine! but this break-up was not all my fault, and she, she says here,  \u0093if you accept full responsibility...\u0094  full responsibility! \u0093...i can begin to trust you again. does that seem like something you can do.  does it?!!\u0094", "answer": " no?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " look, ross, you have what you want, you\u0092re back with rachel. if you bring this up now you\u0092re gonna wreck the best thing that even happened to you.", "answer": "  yeah, i know. i mean, no, you\u0092re right. yeah i guess i\u0092ll let it go. but you-you understand how-how hard it is to forget about this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " sure, it\u0092s hard to forget! but that doesn\u0092t mean you have to talk about it! a lot of things happened on that trip that we should never,  ever talk about.", "answer": " what the hell happened on that beach?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": "  hi, ursula.", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " okay, well umm, i know that we haven\u0092t talked in a long time, but umm okay, our mom is not our birth mom. this-this other lady is our birth mom.", "answer": " right, okay, the one that lives in montuak, umm-hmm.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": "  you know her?!", "answer": " no, i umm, i read about her in mom\u0092s suicide note.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " there-there was a suicide note?!  well, do you still have it?", "answer": "  hang on.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " i can\u0092t believe you didn\u0092t tell me there was a suicide note!", "answer": " yeah. so how have you been doing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": "  \u0093good-bye phoebe and ursula. i\u0092ll miss you. p.s. your mom lives in montauk.\u0094 you just wrote this!", "answer": " well, it\u0092s pretty much the gist. well, except for the poem. you read the poem, right?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " noooo!!", "answer": " all right, hang on!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " my god, you can\u0092t even look at me! can you?", "answer": " nope.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": "  hey! phoebe! we can talk to phoebe!!", "answer": " no. i\u0092m-i\u0092m to depressed to talk.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " i\u0092ll give you a thousand dollars to talk to us.", "answer": "  hey, you guys! what do you, what do you think about making that beach trip an annual thing? chandler, monica, and joey: no!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " all right, that\u0092s it, you guys! what happened out there?", "answer": " what? we took a walk, nothing happened. i can back with nothing all over ross and rachel: come on!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " what happened? joey?", "answer": " all right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": "  no! joey, we swore we\u0092d never tell!", "answer": "  they\u0092ll never understand!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " well, we have to say something! we have to get it out! it\u0092s eating me alive!! monica got stung by a jellyfish.", "answer": "  all right!! all right.  i got stung. stung bad. i couldn\u0092t stand. i-i couldn\u0092t walk.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " i was in too much pain.", "answer": " and i was tired from digging the huge hole!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " and then joey remembered something.", "answer": " i\u0092d seen this thing on the discovery channel...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " wait a minute! i saw that! on the discovery channel, yeah! about jellyfish and how if you...  ewwww!! you peed on yourself?! phoebe and rachel: ewwww!!", "answer": " you can\u0092t say that!! you-you don\u0092t know!! i mean i thought i was gonna pass out from the pain! anyway i-i tried, but i-i couldn\u0092t...bend that way. so...  phoebe, ross, and rachel:  ewwww!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " that\u0092s right i stepped up! she\u0092s my friend and she needed help! and if i had too, i\u0092d pee on anyone of you! only, uhh, i couldn\u0092t. i got the stage fright. i wanted to help, but there was too much pressure. so-so i uh, i turned to chandler.", "answer": "  joey kept screaming at me, \u0093do it now! do it!! do it! do it now!!\u0094 sometimes late at night i can still here the screaming.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": "  \u0093...fuchsia and mauvvve. those are the 66 colours of my bedroommmm.\u0094  thank you, thank you. ohh, and i invite you to count the colours in your bedroom.  except for you. you go away.", "answer": " i\u0092ll go in a second, i-i just wanted to tell you that there hasn\u0092t been a day where i didn\u0092t regret giving you up.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " okay, bye.", "answer": " no, i\u0092m not done. i-i-i just want you to know that i, the reason i didn\u0092t look you up was, well i was afraid that you\u0092d react, just well like, the way, the way you\u0092re reacting right now, and can\u0092t we just, y'know, start from here?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " no.", "answer": " sorry. but just one last thing. y'know you came looking for family. i\u0092m family, i\u0092m it. now, now i\u0092m done.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " but, it\u0092s not like we\u0092re losing anything. y'know?", "answer": " yeah, i guess you\u0092re right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " it\u0092s not like we-we know each other or anything. or that have anything in common.", "answer": " well, i don\u0092t know. i mean it\u0092s not like we don\u0092t have anything in common. i mean i like uh, pizza.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " i-i like pizza!", "answer": " you do?! wait, i like umm, the beetles.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " oh my god, so do i!", "answer": " i knew it, wow!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " wait-wait-wait, wait! puppies. cute or ugly?", "answer": " ohh, so cute.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " uh-huh, well! but umm, still i\u0092m-i\u0092m mad at you.", "answer": " i know. i\u0092m mad at me too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " well umm, do you wanna get something to eat? i\u0092m kinda hungry.", "answer": " hey! me too!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " oh-hooo, i missed you.", "answer": " i missed you too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " ooh, i was soo nervous about that letter. but the way you owned up to everything, it just showed me how much you\u0092ve grown. y'know?", "answer": "  i suppose.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " you have! ross, you should give yourself credit. i mean my mom never thought this would work out. it was all, \u0093once a cheater, always a cheater.\u0094", "answer": "  umm-hmm.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": "  we were on a break!!!!!!!", "answer": "   coffee house?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " and for the record, it took two people to break up this relationship!!", "answer": " yeah! you and that girl from that copy place, which yesterday you took full responsibility for!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " i didn\u0092t know what i was taking full responsibility for! okay?! i didn\u0092t finish the whole letter!", "answer": " what?!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " i fell asleep!", "answer": " you fell asleep?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " it was 5:30 in the morning, and you had rambled on for 18 pages. front and back!!   oh-oh-oh, and by the way, y-o-u-apostrophe-r-e means \u0091you are,\u0092 y-o-u-r means \u0091your!\u0092", "answer": " y'know i can\u0092t believe i even thought about getting back together again! we are so over!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " oh, oh, and hey-hey-hey, those little spelling tips will come in handy when you\u0092re at home on saturday nights playing scrabble with monica!!", "answer": " hey!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": "  sorry!!  i just feel bad about all that sleep you\u0092re gonna miss wishing you were with me!", "answer": " oh, no-no-no don\u0092t you worry about me falling asleep. i still have your letter!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " and hey! just so you know, it\u0092s not that common! it doesn\u0092t happen to every guy! and it is a big deal!!", "answer": " i knew it!!!! closing credits", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": "  gin.", "answer": " we were playing gin? y'know if we were a couple, we could play this game naked.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " will you stop!", "answer": " okay. all right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}]